电视:今天在青年透视杂志上公布了对青年情侣的年度调查结果,柯克被他们视为梦中情人.
TV: And on the lighter side of the news Teen Scene magazine today released
the results of its annual Teen Heartthrob poll.
They have declared that the dreamiest guy alive is Kirk...
本:管他哪?
Ben: Who cares?
迈克:你在看什么?
Mike: What are you watching?
本:没什么节目.
Ben: Nothing's on.
迈克:骗人!明明是有节目的.
Mike: No, there's gotta be.
本:你不准看电视了,因为你已经答应过爸爸和妈妈了,
Ben: Anyway you're not supposed to watch TV.
快去做功课吧!
You promised Mom and Dad you'd actually do your homework for a change.
迈克:好了!别再吵了,我记得呢!
Mike: Hey, don't sweat it.I will.
电视:海狸-自然界最着名的工程师.
TV: More properly known as the castori is one of nature's most ambitious
engineers.
迈克:你不是说没什么节目嘛!
Mike: And you said nothing was on.
开萝尔:好啊!迈克,
Carol: Why Mike, what in the world are you doing in here when you have
你在这里干什么,别忘了你还有一篇英语作文没写好.
that darn English report due?
杰森:什么?迈克!
Jason: What?Mike!
迈克:开萝尔,难道你就不能代我写一下?
Mike: I'll get you for this Carol.
杰森:迈克,你不是已经向我发过誓说回家就做作业的,
Jason: Mike, didn't you put your hand on your heart and promise to do
怎么现在就忘了?
your homework?
迈克:爸爸,我记得.
Mike: Dad, I will.
杰森:那好,我们还要做什么?难道还要付你做作业的工钱吗?
Jason: Well, what do we have to do?Pay you to do it?
迈克:爸爸,你知道你还有很多别的事要做.
Mike: You know, I think you're on to something here, Dad.
麦琪:嘿!PBS的海狸专题还在播吗?
Maggie: Oh, hey.Is that that PBS beaver special on yet?
迈克,你该去做作业了.
Mike, you are supposed to be doing...
迈克:我知道要做我的英语作文,你们都怎么了,
Mike: Doing my English homework.I know.What is it with you people?
弄得好像我从不做作业或其他事似的.
You act like I never do my homework or something.
每个人:嗯哼!
Everybody: Uh-huh.
迈克:得了,
Mike: Come on!Look,
不就是一篇评论雷蒙德·钱德勒的四页小短文嘛.
it's a crummy little four page English report on Raymond Chandler.
麦琪:是必须要打印出来的四页.
Maggie: Four pages that are typed.
杰森:要有个人见解.
Jason: Researched.
麦琪:要有注解.
Maggie: Footnoted.
杰森:同时列出参考书目.
Jason: With bibliography.
麦琪:本来可以是在四个星期内完成.
Maggie: That you should have been working on for four weeks.
杰森:但现在明天就得交,而且……
Jason: And that is due tomorrow!And...
麦琪:按你的老师讲……
Maggie: According to your teacher...
杰森:如果你连B都没拿到……
Jason: If you don't get at least a B on this...
麦琪:那就不能通过这么课,这就意味着你……
Maggie: You won't pass the course and that means that you...
开萝尔:不能顺利毕业.
Carol: Won't graduate.
本:太好了!
Ben: Yea!
迈克:你们怎么回事?是不是一起演练过台词?
Mike: What'd you guys do?Get together and rehearse this or something?
杰森:迈克!
Jason: Mike.
迈克:爸爸妈妈,你们不要这么激动,好吗?
Mike: Mom!Dad!Look, you don't have to get so excited.
杰森:什么?叫我们别激动?
Jason: Oh, we don't?
迈克:听我讲,
Mike: Look, I know over the years my school record hasn't exactly been
的确这几年我的成绩一直不是很理想.
terrific.
开萝尔:什么?
Carol: What?
本:哇!
Ben: Whoa!
迈克:请相信我,
Mike: But believe me, I know how important this report is.
我知道这次的作业非常重要.其实我也很着急,
I know I kid around a lot,
我没理由甘心不及格.
but there is no way I'm gonna let myself fail this course.
爸,我已经读过那本书,
I mean, Dad, I've even read the book!
今晚我什么都不想了,
And that's why I have set everything aside this evening so I can spend
我要把自己关在房间里,然后在书桌上用整晚的时间完成作文,
the entire night in my room, at my desk,
无论作文有多长.
finishing that report no matter how long it takes.
波纳:有人吗?迈克,对不起,我迟到了.你准备好了没?
Boner: Hello?Mikey, sorry, I'm late.Ready to split?
杰森:迈克,你在说谎!今晚你是想出去!
Jason: Mike you're lying!You were planning on going out tonight!
迈克:爸爸,
Mike: Well, Dad.If by out you mean taking off and messing around until
你是怎么了?如果你是把准备好了没理解成为外出游荡直至最后忘记重要的英语作业的话,
all hours forgetting about my very important English assignment,
那你就错了.
you are so wrong.
波纳:不是吗?
Boner: They are?
杰森:迈克,那么你想要干什么?
Jason: So, what were your plans, Mike?
本:看他跳舞!
Ben: Watch him dance!
迈克:好吧,是这样的.
Mike: Well, ok, alright.
波纳和我准备出去几分钟,
Boner and I were merely going to take a couple of minutes to drop in on
见见一位非常非常亲密的朋友,
a very dear, very close friend of ours who is very nervous about this
她对新工作还不太适应,我们想给她一些帮助.
new job and who needs some support.
本:哦,你真个好人!
Ben: Oh, man, he's good!
杰森:那么这位非常非常亲密的朋友到底是谁哪?
Jason: So, who exactly is this very dear, very close friend?
迈克:谁?唉,名字一下子突然想不起了.
Mike: Who?Well, you know, the name's kinda slipping my mind.
波纳:仙娜·沃沃·贝克维茨.
Boner: Sheena Woo-woo Berkowitz.
麦琪:哦!天哪!
Maggie: Oh, brother.
迈克:好吧,听我讲,
Mike: Ok, alright.Now before you jump to the wrong conclusion here,
仙娜是努力了很久,
just know that Sheena just got a very challenging job at Abozaban Pizza
才在那家意大利馅饼店找到这份工作的,是抛生面团的.
throwing dough in the air.
波纳:哦,是的.
Boner: Oh, yea.
开萝尔:但是妈妈,仙娜可是个什么也不会的人.
Carol: And Mom, Sheena's famous for needing all kinds of support.
波纳:哦,是的.
Boner: Oh, yea.
杰森:波纳,你现在就给我离开!
Jason: Boner, get out!
麦琪:杰森,你太粗鲁了!
Maggie: Jason, that's rude.
杰森:请谅解.
Jason: Sorry.
麦琪:迈克,
Maggie: Mike go to your room.
马上回你的房间里做你的英语作业.
Go straight to your room and get started on your paper.
麦克:但是我……
Mike: But, what...
杰森:在你完成作业前都不许出来,
Jason: And don't come out of your room until you either finish that homework
否则你别想拿到一分零用钱.
or you turn 21,whichever comes first.
波纳:迈克,他们整晚都要把你关着吗?
Boner: You tied up all night, Mikey?
麦琪:波纳,你现在马上给我离开!
Maggie: Boner, get out!
本:女士们,先生们,迈克引起公愤了,现在他真想讲书本狠狠地揍一顿.
Ben: And the crowd is stunned, ladies and gentleman.Mike Seaver is actually gonna hit
the books
杰森:你俩还坐在干什么?
Jason: And what are you kids sitting around for?
难道没有其他事了吗?
Don't you have some chores to do?
麦琪:今天是该谁倒垃圾?
Maggie: Whose night is it to take out the trash?
本和开萝尔:是迈克!
Ben and Carol: Mike's!
杰森:迈克,把垃圾倒掉!
Jason: Mike, take out the trash!
迈克:什么?
Mike: What?
麦琪:迈克,今晚该你倒垃圾了.
Maggie: Mike, it's your night to take out the garbage.
迈克:但是我的作业还没完成呀.
Mike: But I have to work on my report.
杰森:好的,先倒完垃圾再去做作业.
Jason: Well, you do that after the trash.
Mike: Oh, ok!Alright, fine!But if I don't at least get a B on
this report.It's on your heads
波纳:哇!32秒,还不赖.
Boner: Ba-bing!Thirty-two seconds.Not bad.
迈克:哦,不不,波纳,我还没脱身呐.
Mike: Oh, no.I didn't get out of it, Bone.
波纳:这我明白,听着,沃沃她要到八点才下班.我真想将那群家伙狠狠揍一顿,然后在窗户上留些记号.
Boner: Yea, right.Sure, listen.Woo-woo's shift ends at eight o'clock.I want to
beat the crowd and get the spot right in front of the window
迈克:不不,我是认真的.我还得去做那烦人的英语作业.
Mike: No, I'm serious, man.I gotta finish my stupid English report.
波纳:迈克,迈克,
Boner: Mikey, Mikey.Think about what counts here!
英语对我们有什么用呢?你不要回去做英语作业了.
You don't got no need for English!
迈克:真是令人难以置信!那家馅饼店我经常去,
Mike: I can't believe it!
谁在里面我都知道,对!
I mean, all my life,
里面还有一个老头叫圭多.现在是这个叫沃沃·贝克维茨的女人,
I've been walking past the windows of pizza parlors and who's always in there?
她抓起一把面团往上抛,
Yea, some porked out old guy named Guido.But now it's Woo-woo Berkowitz.
然后稳稳接住,弯背,
Throwing gobs of dough, high in the air, reaching up to catch them,
伸腰,这简直就是体型和官能完美的结合!
arching her back and stretching.The perfect blend of form and function.
还有那脸,那头发……
The face, the hair...
波纳:就和凤尾鱼一样.
Boner: The anchovies.
迈克:我都愿意付钱看她抛面团,
Mike: You know, I would pay money to see her toss anything in the air.
你知道明晚她还上班吗?
Look, man, there's always tomorrow night, right?
波纳:不,不,
Boner: No, no, no, no.
不,不行,
Not for me, see,
今晚我要去,
I'm going tonight because there could be a nuclear war tomorrow and I
没准明天就爆发核战争,到时我会后悔一辈子的.
would never forgive myself.
迈克:哦,好的,很好,波纳.
Mike: Oh, great.Just great, Bone.
杰森:哦,迈克.
Jason: Oh, Mike.
迈克:哦,爸爸!
Mike: Oh, Dad!
杰森:迈克,
Jason: Yea, Mike.When I saw you out here playing with the basketball,
当我看到你拿着篮球在浪费时光的时候,我就很生气,
just wasting time, I thought to myself well I gotta say,
为什么你就一定要对我说谎呢?
I got to be honest here, I got to tell you right now, Mike,
可换个角度想想,我也许不能这样,
I got angry.Then I thought, no, no, no, no.
说不定这孩子有篮球方面的天赋.
Maybe Mike's really got a future in professional basketball.
因此我就不管你的英语作业,
So, why don't you just forget about that English report, forget about school,
不管学校,不管你只有1米65且很瘦弱的身体.
forget about the fact you're 5'7 and white.
我敢说你要是象这样投篮你就可以离开我们了,
You know, I promised myself, Mike, if you made that last shot, boy,
I'd just let you party!Just sail right on in to that NBA draft
我想你我都很清楚.
I guess we both know what that last air ball cost you.
迈克:波纳,再见.
Mike: Later, Bone.
波纳:一个生面团就把你的生活全搅和了,你爸爸可真是厉害啊!
Boner: Bone, one air ball and your whole life is down the shoot.Your dad is really strict!
迈克:如果你们这些家伙都不相信我,不要绕来绕去,
Mike: Look, if you guys don't have any faith in me,
直接一点.
don't beat around the bush, just say it!
麦琪和杰森:我们信不过你!
Maggie and Jason: We have no faith in you!
迈克:哦!哇!那是什么呀?
Mike: Oh, whoa.What is that?
本:是个穿着比基尼的女人
Ben: It's a woman in a bikini bending over.
迈克:本!老爸老妈知不知道你在看闭路电视?
Mike: Ben!Does Mom and Dad know that you're watching that cable channel?
本:这个不是闭路电视,这是本地新闻.
Ben: This isn't cable, this is the local news.
这星期他们在讨论比基尼的问题.
This week they're examining the bikini question.
迈克:她的电话号码才是我关心的事.唉,
Mike: Yea, the only question I got is what's her phone number?Oh ho ho!
这种节目你最好少看!
Watch out for those nasty waves!
本:我知道36频道有好节目.
Ben: I knew with thirty six channels there had to be something good on.
迈克:哦,快看啊.她全省湿透了.可怜的宝贝,
Mike: Oh, look at that.She's getting all soaking wet.Poor baby!
哦,快看啊!哦,快看啊!
Oh, look at that.Oh, look at that!
麦琪:你为什么不录下来呢?
Maggie: Why don't you videotape it?
迈克:本,真是好主意,快点.哦,妈妈!
Mike: Good idea.Start it now, Ben Oh, Mom!
本:妈妈,录下来也没关系,这只是本地新闻.
Ben: Uh, Mom.This isn't disgusting.This is the local news!
麦琪:今晚也该让电视机休息一下了.
Maggie: The TV stays off for the rest of the night.
本:什么?
Ben: What?
麦琪:抱歉,本,这会令你哥哥分心的.
Maggie: Sorry, Ben.Your brother can't handle the distractions.
本:爸爸!妈妈不让我看新闻!
Ben: Dad!Mom won't let me watch the news!
麦琪:迈克,现在就给我上楼,马上!
Maggie: Mike.Upstairs and I mean now!March!
迈克:马上?得了,
Mike: March?Mom, come on.
妈妈,
Look, we're both adults here and you don't need to treat me like I'm some
我们两个都不是小孩子了,不要老把我当小孩看.
silly, little child.
麦琪:上去!快!
Maggie: Go!Now!
迈克:噢,见鬼了.
Mike: Aw, nuts!
迈克:她居然把我当小孩看.还是开始做事吧,
Mike: Treat me like a little kid, huh?Alright, to work.Hey!Where's my desk?
嘿!我的桌子哪里去了?谁把我的桌子偷走了?
Alright!Who swiped my desk?
杰森:迈克,快点给我做作业!
Jason: Mike, get to work now!
迈克:哦,好吧!没有桌子怎么让我做作业呀?
Mike: Oh, fine.How's a guy supposed to work without a desk?Oh, wait a minute.
哦,等等,在这里呢.
Oh, here it is.Alright.A desk.Now, what else?Typewriter.Hey!Alright.
桌子有了,还要一个打印机,谁把我的打印机偷走了?
Ok, who stole my typewriter?
玛姬:迈克,快点给我做作业!
Maggie: Mike!Get to work!
迈克:好,很好,真是太好了,连打字机也没有,我可怎么打文章啊?哦!还有介绍雷蒙德·钱德勒的书呢?看来是有人偷了我的…….好吧,这么多纸,我只要四张就够了.好吧,首先把纸放进去,运行的还不错,先打我的名字吧.我打到哪了?对了,我的名字.对,挺简单的.不再等等,我还得先打草稿再打字.还要一支软芯铅笔2号.对,对,很好.现在开始写吧!
Mike: Oh, great.Just great, Mom.How's a guy supposed to type a stupid report
when he Ow.Ok, now, where's the Raymond Chandler book?Oh, great.Hey!
Somebody stole
my... Ok.Oh, that's a lot of paper.I only need four pieces.Ok.First
I'll start with putting the paper in.Alright.Not bad.Alright, now, my name.Alright
Where was I?Oh, yea.My name.Alright.This is easy.No, no.wait.I
should write this out before I type it.Alright.Hm.Tyconda Ropa 2.Soft.Oh, oh
great!Just when I'm starting to go
开萝尔:迈克,我不会帮你写的.
Carol: No, Mike.I am not helping you with your paper.
迈克:你怎么知道是我的?
Mike: How'd you know it was me?
开萝尔:因为只有你才会这样敲门,快给我走开.
Carol: Cause it was a dumb sounding knock.Get out.
迈克:得了,
Mike: Oh, well, for your information,
我来不是让你同情我的,
I did not come in here for your pathetic help.
我只是想削一下铅笔.
I'm merely here to sharpen a pencil.
开萝尔:那好吧!铅笔机在那边,不过不太好用.
Carol: Alright, over there.The pencil sharpener's a little tricky to...
迈克:对你来说可能不太好用,对我们男人来说这只是小菜一碟.哦,
Mike: Well, maybe for you but men are much better at handling power tools.
谢了!开萝尔,那现在我应该怎么做?
Oh, thanks a lot,Carol!Now, what am I supposed to do?
开萝尔:我想你的作文要用打印机打出了.
Carol: I thought your paper had to be typed anyway.
迈克:是的,但是总得有个草稿吧,你知道什么吗?
Mike: Yea, but you got to have a first draft first.Don't you know anything?
开萝尔:你是说你还没有开始写?
Carol: You mean you haven't even started yet?
迈克:得了,我只是想听听你的意见.
Mike: Hey, look, what's your point?
开萝尔:你自己的呢?
Carol: 4.0, what's yours?
迈克:开萝尔,听着,作文全装在这里.
Mike: Look, Carol.I have got the whole report right up here.
开萝尔:这才叫安全.
Carol: Where it's safe.
迈克:快讲讲你的看法?
Mike: What do you know anyway?
开萝尔:我对雷蒙德·钱德勒的作品只有一些初浅的看法,
Carol: I know that a cursory examination of Raymond Chandler's work won't
这些看法并不能揭示出作者在作品中所表现那种深遂和具有象征主义色彩的感情,
reveal the full extent of the depth, symbolism,
就以友谊天长地久为例,
and import that he weaves into his stories.
雷蒙德·钱德勒……
I mean, take The Long Goodbye, for example, I mean, here Chandler...
等等,哦,测试一二三,
Mike: Wait, wait!Please oh please oh please!Testing one two three!
开始,开始,开始.
Please work, please work, please work!
录音机:测试一二三,开始,开始,开始.
Recorder: Testing one two three!Please work, please work, please work!
迈克:你说什么?
Mike: Oh, yea?
开萝尔:什么什么?
Carol: Oh, yea, what?
迈克:好吧,
Mike: Well, I was saying you were totally wrong about what you were saying
我是说你刚才讲的全是错的
before.
开萝尔:我是怎么说的?
Carol: What was I saying?
迈克:哦,你说雷蒙德·钱德勒学过打击乐.
Mike: Oh, well, you know, about Raymond Chandler playing the cymbals.
开萝尔:不是的,迈克.我是说他的作品内涵深刻且具有象征主义色彩.
Carol: No, Mike.I said his work was fraught with symbolism and import.
迈克:对的对的,但是你怎么证明呐?
Mike: Oh, right, right.Well, uh, prove it.
开萝尔:证明?
Carol: Prove it?
迈克:是的.
Mike: Yea.
开萝尔:迈克,
Carol: Well, Mike, you need only read The Long Goodbye to see how Chandler
你去看看,
used the metaphor of the 40's gumshoe to illustrate the plight of the
想象一下雷蒙德是怎么运用比喻手法来说明二十世纪的现代人是如何与困境做斗争的.
modern man in the twentieth century, alone to fight the incredible odds.
我的意思是,
I mean, essentially, Chandler's message was that modern man hadn't traveled
雷蒙德想要表达的思想是现代生活和乔叟那个时代的生活差距并不太大.
that far since Chaucerian days.
麦琪:够了,开萝尔.
Maggie: That's enough, Carol.
开萝尔:我作什么了?
Carol: What'd I do?
麦琪:我猜你哥哥已经差不多完成作文了.
Maggie: Well, I guess about most of your brother's paper.
迈克:哦,好了!
Mike: Oh, come on.Mom, that is such an insult.
妈妈,你这么讲对我来说是一种侮辱.你难道真的以为我会让妹妹帮我完成作业?
You actually think that I would have my little sister do my work for me?
麦琪:是你自己说的哦
Maggie: You were saying?
迈克:嘿!是谁把这个东西放到的口袋里的?听着开萝尔,我写的会比你更好的.
Mike: Hey!Alright, who put that in my pocket?I expected better of you, Carol.
麦琪:不要再找借口了.
Maggie: Not one more lame excuse.
迈克:但是,妈妈,我……
Mike: But, Mom, I
麦琪:别废话了
Maggie: Not one more word!
迈克:不过……
Mike: Just...
麦琪:我不想听了.
Maggie: Not one syllable!
迈克:但是……
Mike: But...
麦琪:不要再讲了.
Maggie: Not one letter.
从现在开始,在你完整地打出整篇作文之前,
Now, you are not to set foot outside this room until you have typed one
别想离开你的房间半步.
entire page.If you understand me, bink' your eyes.
迈克:知道了.
Mike: Bink'?
麦琪:好了,迈克,是你让我采取这种严厉地手段的!本!
Maggie: Ok, Mike, you leave me no choice except to take drastic action!Ben!
迈克:你去干什么?
Mike: What are you going to do?
本:我发誓我没在看新闻!
Ben: I wasn't watching the news!I swear!
麦琪:本,你想挣十块钱吗?
Maggie: Ben, how would you like to make ten dollars?
本:我更愿挣一百块.
Ben: I'd rather make a hundred.
麦琪:就十块.
Maggie: Ten's all.
本:什么工作?
Ben: What's the job?
麦琪:我想让你看守这个房间.
Maggie: I want you to stand guard outside this room.
迈克:什么?
Mike: What?
麦琪:要是迈克离开半步就马上通知我.
Maggie: If Mike comes out for any reason, you let me know.
迈克:妈妈,本可是我的伙伴,
Mike: But, Mom, Mom.
我的兄弟,我的手足呀!
If you think that Benny here, my pal, my bro, my blood,
你要是以为凭十块钱就想让本出卖我,那你就错了.本才不希罕这十块钱呢?
would sell me out for ten dollars, you are so wrong.
对吧?本.
I mean, Benny couldn't live with himself, right?
本:是的 妈妈,我才不希罕这十块钱呐!
Ben: No, Mom.I couldn't.
迈克:看到了吗?
Mike: See?
本:给二十就成交!
Ben: For twenty I could!
麦琪:就十块.
Maggie: Ten.
本:那好,就十块.
Ben: I could live with that.
麦琪:好了,终于大功告成.看来不强硬不行呀!你看现在迈克在房间里,本在门外看着,现在才八点,这样今晚准能完成一篇作文.
Maggie: Well, I think we've finally done it.I had to get tough, but Mike's in his room, Ben's standing guard, it's only 8 o'clock, and with any luck that English report will soon be born.
杰森:太好了,太好了!
Jason: Great, great.
麦琪:你在干什么?
Maggie: What are you doing?
杰森:在看电视.
Jason: I'm, uh, watching TV.
麦琪:怎么没声音呀?
Maggie: Why can't I hear anything?
杰森:我把声音关了,怕影响迈克做作业.
Jason: Oh, I left the sound off so I wouldn't disturb Mike.
麦琪:亲爱的,你想的太周全了,
Maggie: Well, that's very sweet honey,
不过没声音怎么看呀?
but what can you watch without the sound?
杰森:这只是个专题新闻,
Jason: This is news special.
好像是对比基尼问题做深入的分析.
It's an in-depth examination of the bikini question.
麦琪:我想这下不会再有什么问题了
Maggie: I didn't know there was a question.
杰森:哦,是的
Jason: Oh, yea.
麦琪:下面该你了!
Maggie: Your turn!
杰森:本,让一下.
Jason: Out of the way, Ben.
本:你来这里妈妈知道吗?
Ben: Has this visit been cleared by Mom?
杰森:是的
Jason: It has, yes.
本:那有妈妈写的条子吗?
Ben: You got something on paper?
杰森:快让开!帽子不错.
Jason: Out of the way!Nice hat.
迈克:谢谢,我刚刚用音乐振奋了一下精神,爸爸.
Mike: Thanks.Yea, I was just gearing up a little mood music, Dad.
杰森:现在还很兴奋嘛!
Jason: In the mood now?
迈克:是的!
Mike: Yea!
杰森:很好.
Jason: Good.
迈克:可以了!
Mike: Yea!
杰森:迈克,这是抵押品.
Jason: Cause this is a hostage, Mike.
迈克:爸爸!
Mike: Dad!
杰森:没什么好讲的了!那你的作文来交换,
Jason: And this is a non-negotiable demand!I want the English report.
否则别想再见到这台音响.
Or you will never see your stereo alive again.
迈克:嘿嘿!爸爸小心电线.
Mike: Hey, hey!Dad watch out for the...
麦琪:到底怎么了?
Maggie: What the heck happened?
杰森:现在他没有音乐,没有朋友,
Jason: He has no music, no friends,
没有食物,除非什么东西能从他床底下钻出来.
no food except for whatever might be growing under his bed.
这样他就不会再分心了,唯一可干的事就是完成作文了.
And no more distractions, nothing.Nothing to do except finish his paper.
哦,比基尼问题讨论的怎么样了?
Aw, whatever happened to the bikini question?
麦琪:他们讨论的结果是出来了,答案是反对.
Maggie: They answered it.It was no.'
你肯定迈克现在没什么其他事可做了吗?
Are you sure there's nothing else up there for him to do?
杰森:没了!除非他想清理房间.
Jason: Nothing!Unless, he decides to clean up his room.
麦琪和杰森:不会的.
Maggie and Jason: Nah.
迈克:好了,现在要工作了.
Mike: Alright, now I can work.Ok.Ok.And there it is fans!Unbelievable!
这真是令人难以置信啊!迈克·西沃已经打破了用鼻子卷铅笔的记录,
Michael Seaver just broken the all time record for nose balancing a pencil!
女士们,先生们,
And now, ladies and gentleman, the impossible.
更绝的是,西沃打算用两支铅笔来表演.但愿里面有电池,
The Seaver's gonna try not with one, but two pencils!
我保证开车时速控制在三十以内.好,
Oh, please let there be batteries!Please let there be batteries!
很好,西沃准备工作了,
I'll never drive over thirty-five again!Oh, yes!Alright!
准备好了,准备好了.
The Seave's ready to work.I'm talkin' ready!I'm ready.
收音机:长岛时间八点三十五,现在是点播节目,这首歌献给迈克
Radio: 8:35pm in Long Island, it's request time!And this one goes out to Mike!
迈克:哇!
Mike: Whoa.
收音机:迈克,这是你的梦中女孩蒂凡妮,
Radio: Mike, from your dream girl, brand new tune now.
她是唱流行歌曲的,现在她是全国最红的歌星(歌曲).
From hottest new singer in the country, Tiffany.
唱歌
(sing)
杰森:嘿,本.
Jason: Hey, Ben.
本:那里也别想去,傻瓜!
Ben: You're not going anywhere, dirt bag!
杰森:干得好!现在你该回去睡觉了
Jason: That's alright...You've done a good job.Good boy.You can go to bed now.
本:你们不用付我酬金给我,我只是开玩笑的.爸爸,
Ben: You guys don't have to pay me.I had fun.Don't get excited, Dad.
别高兴的太早,还是要收钱的,我只是开你玩笑.
I was just kidding.
麦琪:晚安,亲爱的.
Maggie: Good night, honey.
杰森:好了,他要么在做作业.
Jason: Well, either he's working.
麦琪:要么就是跳窗逃走了,再要么就是睡着了.
Maggie: Or he escaped out the window.Or he fell asleep working.
杰森:看看他写的作文.首先……
Jason: Let's see how he did.The.'
麦琪:念啊.
Maggie: Go on.
杰森:没有了.
Jason: There is no on.
麦琪:迈克
Maggie: Mike!
迈克:哦,妈妈!妈妈!这摇滚音乐太爽了!
Mike: Oh, uh, Mom!Mom!I'm doing great here.I'm on a roll!
哦,爸爸,你也在啊!
Oh, Dad, you're here, too!
杰森:什么?你在听摇滚乐,
Jason: Oh, you're on a roll?This is a roll?
一个半小时过去了,你就写了这么几个字!
One word, one lousy syllable in an hour and a half?
迈克:是啊!但我对拼对了呀!
Mike: Yea, but I spelled it right.
麦琪:哦!迈克,不要开玩笑!
Maggie: Oh, Mike, that's not funny!
迈克:我是很想和你们多聊一会,
Mike: Mom, look, I really wish I had more time to chat,
但是我还得写作文.
but this report is due pretty soon.
麦琪:迈克,这一点都不好笑!
Maggie: Mike, this is not cute, amusing, or charming!
麦克:好吧,妈妈.
Mike: Well, Mom.
杰森:我实在没办法了!
Jason: I give up!
麦琪:我不会放弃的!
Maggie: Well, I don't!
杰森:哦!麦琪,
Jason: Aw, Maggie.Come on.We can't help him anymore.
我们不要在他身上白花苦心了,
It's not enough for us to want things for him.
也不要对他寄于厚望了,一点上进心也没有人只被做个要饭的!
He's gotta want them for himself.And apparently all he wants is to be a bum.
麦克:爸爸,你们真的生我的气了?
Mike: You're really mad at me, aren't you Dad?
麦琪:是的.
Maggie: Yes!
杰森:不.
Jason: No.
麦琪:不?
Maggie: No?
杰森:是的,我在生我自己的气,
Jason: No!I'm mad at myself!
原以为你是一个聪明且前途光明的孩子,
Oh, I believed, I really believed that you were just, well,
只是有点懒惰.
you were bright and intelligent, just a little bit lazy.
我想总会有一天你会克服这些缺点,但是到现在我才发现我是在自欺欺人.
I thought maybe some day you'd snap out of it but, I've been kidding myself.
迈克:你说什么?
Mike: What are you saying?
麦琪:他不是那个意思,杰森,
Maggie: Nothing that he means.
快告诉迈克你不是那个意思!
Jason, tell Mike you don't mean a word that you're saying.
杰森:我就是这个意思,麦琪,
Jason: I do mean it.
我想我们该到承认错误的时候了!
I just think it's time, Maggie, that we should admit we're wrong.
迈克:什么?你们什么错了?
Mike: About what?What are you wrong about, huh?
杰森:嘿,我们还是不要徒劳了,
Jason: Hey, come on.We've been pushing you to realize your big potential.
我们本想极力地帮你认识到你自己的潜力,现在看来你的潜力是已经挖掘完了.
Maybe this is all the potential you've got.
迈克:不是这样的!
Mike: It is not!
麦琪:杰森!
Maggie: Jason!
杰森:麦琪,我只能这么解释了.
Jason: Well, that's the only explanation, Maggie.
迈克:爸爸,不要这样了!
Mike: No, it isn't, Dad.Look, come on.I'm a goof!A clown!A total bozo!
你瞧,我承认我不务正业和游手好闲,但是我的脑子还是挺好使的.
But I am not stupid!
麦琪:迈克,我肯定你是个大笨蛋!
Maggie: Mike, I believe you're a total bozo.
迈克:谢谢你,妈妈.
Mike: Thanks, Mom.
麦琪:杰森,你不会是认真的吧
Maggie: Jason, what the you didn't mean that.
杰森:当然,我只是说说而已.
Jason: Well, of course, I didn't mean that.
麦琪:但你当时好像挺当真的!
Maggie: But you sounded so convincing.
杰森:哦!我到希望如此.
Jason: Well, I hope so.
麦琪:杰森,我想你早该对迈克这样了,现在你去哪?
杰森:我还想用这招去弄醒本,对他说他令我很失望.
00:22:10,700
Maggie: Jason, you should've started insulting Mike years ago.Where you going? Jason: Well, now that I'm on a roll I think I'll go wake up Ben and tell him how disappointed I am in him.